the-mainboard.com 2011-03-19

# Privacy Policy | The Mainboard

1.         General

TMB Online LLC and its affiliated companies ("TMB") respects the privacy of every individual who visits this Web site, [www.the-mainboard.com](http://www.the-mainboard.com/ "www.the-mainboard.com") (the "Site"), and all other Web sites owned, operated or maintained directly or indirectly by TMB Online LLC (the "TMB Sites"). TMB has created this statement (the "Privacy Policy") to inform you of TMB’ privacy practices and the terms and conditions under which data that we collect from you on the TMB Sites will be used, shared and otherwise treated. This Privacy Policy will also instruct you on how you can verify the accuracy, and control certain uses, of the information you provide to us on the TMB Sites.

2.         Collection and Use of Information

Personally Identifiable Information

When you visit the TMB Sites, you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information about yourself ("PII") for certain purposes such as providing the service for which your information was requested, or enhancing your experience on the TMB Sites (for a fuller description, see "Use of Your Information" below). PII may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and telephone number, and for online transactions, billing and shipping information, and credit card information.

Providing PII to the TMB Sites is on a strictly voluntary basis, however, if you opt not to provide the TMB Sites with certain PII (See procedures in Article VI below ("Opt-Out")), you may be unable to participate in certain promotions, receive product information, or buy products offered directly or indirectly through the TMB Sites.

You acknowledge and agree that your provision of Your Information to the TMB Sites will be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and that TMB may use Your Information for the purposes stated herein, including carrying out the purposes for which such information was collected. As set forth in more detail below, TMB will not share your information with any third party or unrelated website.

In some cases, you may be requested to provide the TMB Sites with certain information about you that is not personally identifiable, such as your age, zip code, make-up preferences, shopping habits and other buying preferences, product and information preferences, and personal characteristics and other traits ("NPII", and together, with your PII, "Your Information"). We may also collect certain information about your use of the TMB Sites and other Web sites linked to the TMB Sites, such as the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to the TMB Sites.

We may also use a technology known as "cookies" (or any other technology now existing or hereafter developed providing similar tracking benefits to TMB) to help you travel through the TMB Sites and other Web sites linked to the TMB Sites more easily and to help us understand how you and others use the TMB Sites and other Web sites linked to the TMB Sites. Specifically, we may use cookies (or such other technology) to: i) customize your visitation and shopping experience on the TMB Sites and other Web sites linked to the TMB Sites; ii) provide you with custom-tailored content; iii) notify you of certain promotions, products and services that TMB and other companies believe may be of interest to you; and iv) for any other purpose permitted under applicable law from time to time. Cookies are used by almost every Web site for these and similar purposes. You may, however, disallow reception of cookies at any time by resetting your web browser. Most Internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.

Use of Your Information

TMB may store and process Your Information in order to carry out the purpose for which such information was provided, which purposes you acknowledge includes the general promotion, marketing, and advertising activities related to the services that TMB makes available from time to time, as well as for purposes ancillary to such promotion, marketing and advertising activities and in connection with any other lawful activity that TMB, directly or indirectly, engages in from time to time. Further, you understand and agree that TMB has the unrestricted right to use such data for any and all lawful purposes.

When you register on one of the TMB Sites, we may ask you to provide your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone numbers, and other PII. This allows the TMB Sites to maintain a user profile of each user so that we may customize preferences for each specific user, provide a faster method for Web visitors to submit information to TMB (and receive back either the information or products desired by each such user), notify users about important functionality changes to the TMB Sites and about new products and services offered by TMB and special offers that we believe users will find to be valuable, as well as generally allow us to better know our users and possibly tailor any specific features, promotions or other notifications to them.

Additionally, if you choose to use TMB’s services, make a purchase online or enter a contest, you may also be given the opportunity to receive additional information about TMB (and other companies with which TMB shares Your Personal Information, as discussed below) and other products and services that TMB and such other companies have available from time to time. Certain services available on the TMB Sites may be provided by third parties, including without limitation, sub-contractors, authorized vendors, event co-sponsors and fulfillment companies, and TMB may provide Your Information to such third parties in order to deliver the requested service to you. For example, if you choose to purchase products or services from the TMB Sites or Web sites linked to the TMB Sites, Your Information provided in connection with such purchase may be made available to an authorized vendor to fulfill that order. TMB may also enhance or merge Your Information with data obtained from third parties, such as information provided by a co-sponsor of a particular promotion, which TMB may use in pursuit of the broad purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy.

In addition to the foregoing circumstances, Your Information may be shared with employees, agents, and independent contractors of TMB and/or with other third parties with whom TMB does business from time to time, including customer support specialists, Web hosting companies, fulfillment companies, and data analysis firms, in connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for TMB, for themselves or for any other lawful purpose. PII submitted to TMB over the TMB Sites in connection with employment inquiries will be used only by TMB and its employees, agents, independent contractors and/or other third parties in your application process and as may be required under applicable laws.  That said, your information will be provided under a Confidentiality Agreement that will prevent such affiliated business or employee from divulging your PII to any third party.

Public Forums

From time to time you may be able to participate in certain activities on the TMB Sites, such as chat rooms or bulletin boards, which will allow you the opportunity to communicate with TMB or other users of the TMB Sites. Unless otherwise noted, these activities are generally accessible to all users of the TMB Sites and any information that you post or otherwise make available through these forums will be non-confidential and known to all other users. Accordingly, please exercise discretion when using these forums. You acknowledge and agree that TMB does not review, censor, or in any manner control the content of these forums and consequently TMB has no liability or responsibility whatsoever for information made available through these forums and that you will be liable to TMB for any liability that we incur as a result of any statement made by you in these forums. Your use of these forums is also subject to [TMB’s Terms and Conditions](http://www.the-mainboard.com/drupal/terms-use) .

3.         Security

TMB is committed to safeguarding and protecting Your Information from loss, misuse or alteration. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and the TMB Sites, and the TMB Sites and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. So even though we pledge to keep your confidential information private, and not share it with third-parties, Users of the TMB Sites use these sites at their own risk, and understand that even though TMB may use its best efforts to prevent your information from being accessed in an unauthorized fashion, it may nevertheless happen due to hacking or some other illicit means by a third party.

In an attempt to enhance the experience of visiting the TMB Sites, TMB may choose to link the TMB Sites to various third party Web sites. However, TMB may have no control over the acts or omissions of these linked Web sites who each should have their own privacy policy and data collection practices, independent of TMB and the TMB Sites. TMB has no liability or responsibility whatsoever for these linked Web sites or for their policies, practices and content. TMB provides these links for the convenience of the visitors to the TMB Sites and such visitors access these sites at their own risk.

4.         Children

TMB is concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. However, the TMB Sites are neither directed nor targeted to children under 13 years old. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, TMB has no intention to knowingly collect any PII (personally identifiable information, such as name, address, telephone number, age or email address) from individuals under the age of thirteen (13) years. If TMB learns that a child under the age of 13 years has provided PII (personally identifiable information) to the TMB Sites without verifiable parental consent, TMB will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from its databases. We strongly encourage parents to monitor their children's use of the Web and we will use our reasonable efforts to delete personally identifiable information that we have received from your under age 13 child from the TMB Sites and our files as set forth above if you send us a request as provided under Article VI below.

5.         Contacting Us Regarding Your Personally Identifiable Information

If you have previously submitted PII to TMB through the TMB Sites, and you would like to review, update, or have your PII information deleted from our databases, please contact us via one of the methods described on our Contact Us page.

6.         Acceptance Of These Terms; Consent to Processing

By using the TMB Sites, you agree to this TMB Privacy Policy and the TMB Terms and Conditions of Use. If you do not so agree, please do not use the TMB Sites. If TMB changes this TMB Privacy Policy or the TMB Terms and Conditions of Use, your continued use of the TMB Sites following the posting of such changes will signify your acceptance of those changes. By providing PII to TMB, you fully and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of Your Information throughout the world, including, without limitation, in the United States and in other countries that may be considered as having less than adequate protection for your PII.

7.         Disclosure Pursuant to Law

TMB may disclose Your Information when required to do so under applicable law.

8.         Inquiries

TMB welcomes your feedback, questions, comments and concerns regarding your use of the TMB Sites and any third party Web sites linked to the TMB Sites. Inquiries regarding the TMB Sites may be made by contacting us via one of the methods described on our contact us page. You can also send us your feedback on any third party sites linked to the TMB Sites.

9.         Amendments To The TMB Privacy Policy

PLEASE NOTE THAT WE MAY CHANGE OUR PRIVACY POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME TO CONFORM TO CHANGES IN THE LAW OR FOR OTHER REASONS, WHICH WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO DO WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT AND SUCH REVISED POLICY WILL BE APPLICABLE TO ANY OF YOUR INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US, WHETHER BEFORE OR AFTER SUCH CHANGE IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. ANY SUCH REVISED PRIVACY POLICY WILL BE POSTED ON THE TMB SITES. AS WE MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME WITHOUT NOTIFYING YOU, WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME TO STAY INFORMED ABOUT HOW WE USE AND PROTECT PII WE COLLECT.
